welcome to category 5 technology TV what
歡迎來到5類科技電視什麼的
you're about to experience is a free
你即將體驗的是免費的
worldwide interactive broadcast from
全球互動廣播
Ontario Canada we broadcast live every
加拿大安大略省每個人都直播
tuesday at seven p.m. eastern time get
星期二晚上七點東部時間到了
your questions in join the community
您加入社區的問題
chat room at triple w category 5 TV or
三聯五類電視或聊天室的聊天室
email us at live at category 5 gb
給我們發送電子郵件，類別為5 gb
and now let's get here's your host Rob a
現在讓我們來看看你的主人Rob a
Ferguson welcome to episode number 207
弗格森歡迎來到第207集
of category 5 technology TV it's so nice
第5類技術電視真是太棒了
to have you here on Tuesday September
能在九月的星期二送你
the 6th pretty while 2011 while already
已經是 2011年的第6名
September what up with that what up with
9月到底是怎麼回事
that as she says my name is Robbie
因為她說我的名字是羅比
Ferguson I'm Hillary Rumble nice to have
弗格森我是希拉里隆隆得很高興
you here nice to see you thank you it's
你在這裡很高興見到你，謝謝你
gonna be here love being here we got
我會在這裡愛到這裡
lots coming up tonight too and lots of
很多人今晚也會來
fun stuff one thing that I've been
有趣的東西，我去過的一件事
looking forward to we've been waiting
期待 我們一直在等待
and waiting because it's we're in the
等待，因為我們在
middle of doing the video productions
在做視頻製作的中間
series we had some server difficulties
系列我們有一些服務器困難
following a power surge and so we have
在電力浪湧之後，我們有了
been able to do all the things that we
能夠做我們所有的事情
wanted to do but one thing that we can
想做的事，但有一點我們可以
do even with limited hardware is stop
即使有限的硬件停止
motion video I'm very excited to be
動畫視頻我很高興能成為
doing that tonight so stick around we're
今晚 這樣 做， 所以堅持我們
gonna learn how to animate mr. Sulu all
要學習如何動畫先生。 蘇祿都
right gonna be great it's gonna be
這將是偉大的，它會是偉大的
awesome fun activity for you and the
對你和你來說真棒的有趣活動
kids or just you yeah yeah like I use
孩子或只是你是啊是的，我喜歡我用
the kids as that as a way of saying you
孩子們這麼說你的一種方式
know I'm not I'm not that big of a geek
知道我不是我不是那麼大的怪人
right it's just this for the kids that
對孩子們來說就是這樣
are the kids I got these dolls cuz you
是我收到這些娃娃的孩子因為你
know the kids love dolls mm-hmm although
知道孩子們喜歡娃娃mm-hmm雖然
they are very cool star trek dolls I
他們是非常酷的星際迷航娃娃我
mean action I should figure it's not
我應該認為不是
adults action figure what was I thinking
成年人的行動圖我在想什麼
that's pretty funny hmm and also coming
這很有趣嗯也來了
up we got a crazy busy world happening
我們發生了一個瘋狂的繁忙世界
in the land of news and I'm going to
在新聞的土地上，我要去
tell you about it right now doom is now
現在就告訴你它現在的厄運
available in Germany 17 years late
17年後在德國上市
though eating a lot of chocolate crust
雖然吃了很多巧克力皮
cuts the risk of heart disease and
減少患心髒病的風險
stroke but there's a catch stick around
中風，但有一個捕獲棒
to find out what that is US scientists
找出那是美國科學家的東西
are warning NASA that the amount of
正在警告美國宇航局的數量
space junk orbiting the Earth has
太空垃圾繞地球軌道運行
reached a tipping point oh and linux is
達到了臨界點哦 和linux是
kernel.org was hacked but we know that
kernel.org被黑了，但我們知道
the linux kernel itself is indeed safe
linux內核本身確實安全
and lastly it may not be up to Vulcan
最後，它可能不是瓦肯人
standards but real life cloaking
標準但真實的隱形
technology really works well in the dark
技術在黑暗中真的很好用
stick around because these stories are
堅持下去因為這些故事
coming up in less than 30 minutes wait a
在不到30分鐘的時間內等待
minute I gotta hear what that's all
我必須聽到這一切
about cloaking technology cloaking
關於隱形技術隱形
technology we gotta turns just turn off
技術我們必須轉身關閉
the lights hey we'll have to find out
燈嘿，我們必須找出來
what that's all about it was can't wait
這一切都是等不及的
it's got to be legit if you're talking
如果你在說話，它必須是合法的
about it I'm too legit to quit so yeah
關於它，我太合法了，所以是的
it's gotta be I love the 80s references
它必須是我喜歡80年代的參考
oh yeah that's how I roll oh yeah we've
哦，是的， 我是如何滾動哦，是的，我們已經
got a couple of viewer testimonials
得到了一些觀眾的推薦
tonight we always welcome your viewer
今晚我們總是歡迎你的觀眾
testimonials on our website category
我們網站類別的推薦書
five dot TV it's just a way of saying
五點電視這只是一種說法
hey to us here at the studio and letting
嘿，我們在工作室和我們在一起
us and other viewers know what you think
我們和其他觀眾都知道你的想法
about the show what you've learned so we
關於這個節目你學到了什麼，所以我們
really appreciate every viewer
非常感謝每一位觀眾
testimonial that comes in we do sure do
我們確實做到的見證
so start this up I'm gonna read you a
所以從頭開始我會讀你的
little something something coming to us
什麼東西來找我們
from fat boy 106 from Nottingham England
來自英國諾丁漢的胖男孩106
hey fat boy 106 I first discovered
嘿胖男孩106我第一次發現
category 5 TV whilst looking for a
5類電視，同時尋找一個
tutorial on how to use the open shot
關於如何使用空位投籃的教程
video editor your tutorial helped me
視頻編輯器您的教程幫助了我
successfully produce my sister's wedding
成功地製作了我姐姐的婚禮
video which she was more than pleased
她非常高興的視頻
with wonderful yeah I continue to learn
非常好，我繼續學習
something new every time I visit
每次我訪問時都會有新的東西
category 5 TV and now see it as one of
5類電視，現在看作是其中之一
the most helpful resources on the web
網上最有用的資源
that's pretty cool that's very cool
這非常酷， 非常酷
thank you very much I would like to
非常感謝你，我想
thank everyone running category 5 TV and
謝謝大家運行5類電視和
its viewers for providing this valuable
它的觀眾提供這種有價值的
source of information thanks fat boy 106
信息來源感謝胖男孩106
for that nice little post we love
對於我們喜歡的那個漂亮的小帖子
hearing from you we also got another one
聽到你的消息我們還有另外一個
here from invisible mutant I'm vincible
這裡來自無形的突變體，我是無形的
what did I say invisible you're still
我說什麼看不見你還在
thinking about the cloaking machine
想著隱形機器
you're right i'm stuck on the cloaking
你是對的，我被困在斗篷上
cuz i'm sewing i'm so excited to hear
因為我縫製我很高興聽到
about the cloaking machine to my
關於我的隱形機
goodness gracious invincible mutant oh
善良親切的無敵變種哦
yay okay hi robbie and crew anybody for
好吧好吧， 羅比和船員任何人
half the second or third testimonial
第二或第三個證言的一半
that i posted here i just couldn't help
我發佈在這裡， 我 忍不住了
myself from not doing this Robbie and
我自己從不做這個 羅比和
his lovely crew deserves something
他可愛的船員值得一試
better from the community this is the
更好地從社區這是
most fantastic tech show channel I have
我擁有的最精彩的科技節目頻道
ever
曾經
watch the incentive to watch this is
注意看這個的動機
uncountable prizes to be won
贏得無數獎品
good-looking and sweet faces oh he must
他必須有好看和甜美的面孔哦
be talking about this guy right here I'm
在這裡談論這個人我是
telling ya not like God to say lovely
告訴你不要像上帝說的那樣可愛
voices and interesting content if I just
如果我只是聲音和有趣的內容
a live show I will never miss the
現場表演我永遠不會錯過
recorded one however the live shows have
然而，錄製了一個現場表演
more fun interactivity and lots of
更有趣的互動性和很多
surprises I am impatient to see how the
我很不耐煩地看到了
new broadcast system would perform what
新廣播系統將執行什麼
kind of bells and whistles would you
你會不會有鐘聲和口哨聲
robbie and crew adds the impressive
羅比和船員增添了令人印象深刻的
machine specs hmm keep it up the IT
機器規格hmm讓它保持IT
world is so much more cheerful with all
世界對所有人來說都更加開朗
of you you've changed the traditional
你改變了傳統
image and dull impression of geeks
極客的形象和沈悶的印象
including me thanks bro invincible where
包括我在內的感謝兄弟無敵
are we just talking about that being a
我們只是在談論那是一個
being a geek it's a very cool action
作為一個極客，這是一​​個非常酷的行動
figure invincible mutant hey hey thanks
圖無敵突變嘿嘿謝謝
for the viewer testimonial what would I
對於觀眾見證我會是什麼
do to improve upon the specs of the cool
做改進酷的規格
new server that we're putting together
我們正在整理的新服務器
you can find out more about the new
你可以找到更多 關於新的
broadcast system on our website category
我們網站類別的廣播系統
5 TV I think it's it's going to do
5電視我覺得它會發生
pretty well for us the one thing that
對我們來說很好的一件事
that we we unfortunately don't have the
我們不幸的是沒有
budget for right now is the solid state
目前的預算是固態
hard drives after it's all said and done
所有的說法和完成後的硬盤驅動器
because the original server we were
因為我們原來的服務器
going to purchase was a used server for
去購買是一個二手服務器
500 bucks so we budgeted 500 and that
500美元，所以我們預算500和那個
became unavailable so in order to go
變得不可用所以為了去
forward we had to purchase om parts so
我們不得不購買om部件
and that ended up costing a little bit
最終花費了一點點
more so that ate into our hard drive
更讓我們吃進硬盤
budget so we're gonna have to use
預算所以我們將不得不使用
spinning hard disks reason I actually
旋轉硬盤的原因我其實
want to use solid-state isn't so much
想要使用固態並不是那麼多
for the speed anymore because I realized
為了速度，因為我意識到了
that a raid 0 like a 2dr or 4dr or 80
raid 0喜歡2dr或4dr或80
will perform very very well but one of
將表現得非常好，但其中一個
the things that I really want to be
我真正想要的東西
doing more of in the future is to be
在未來做更多的事情就是
able to take category 5 on the road so
能夠在路上 上第5類
that means packing up our gear going to
這意味著收拾我們的裝備去
a venue doing a show live from whatever
從任何地方進行表演的場地
spot so one of the reasons I want to go
現場所以我想去的原因之一
with solid-state that's non spinning
固態不旋轉
disks is so that we don't run the risk
磁盤使我們不會冒風險
of if somebody bumps it or if it if it
如果有人碰到它或者如果有的話
gets nudged a little bit when it's
什麼時候輕推一下
getting moved to and from there's less
變得越來越少
chance of actual physical
實際身體的機會
hard drive failure so so that's the one
硬盤驅動器故障所以這就是那個
thing I would improve upon and I think
我會改進的，我想
and we eventually will but to start I
我們最終只會開始我
think the specs that we've laid out are
認為我們已經制定的規範是
going to be fantastic so and thanks for
會很棒，所以 感謝你
the viewer testimonial if you'd like to
觀眾見證如果你願意的話
submit a viewer testimonial to us you
向我們提交觀眾推薦信
can do so a category 5 TV click on
可以這樣做5類電視點擊
interact and you'll see viewer
互動，你會看到觀眾
testimonials and submit your own we
推薦並提交您自己的
would appreciate that mm-hmm hey did it
我會很感激mm-hmm嘿嘿
invincible mutant send you a groovy
無敵突變體送你一個常規
awesome sweet picture groovy awesome one
令人敬畏的甜蜜圖片groovy真棒一個
I'm gonna be hated invincible mutant has
我會被恨無敵突變體了
his office set up in such a way that you
他的辦公室以你這樣的方式建立
can watch the show up on the screen up
可以在屏幕上觀看節目
at the top and then have chat room
在頂部 ，然後有聊天室
running on the laptop below or whatever
在下面的筆記本電腦上運行或任何
else and he says that the other cool
別的，他說另一個很酷
thing about having the screen up at the
有關屏幕的問題
top for the actual viewing experience is
頂級的實際觀看體驗是
the fact that if there are other people
事實上，如果有其他人
in the room it's easier for them to be
在房間裡，他們更容易
able to see what's going on in the show
能夠看到 節目中 發生 了 什麼
they don't need to see the chat room on
他們不需要 看到聊天室
this laptop me over so that's very cool
這台筆記本電腦讓我非常酷
I'll a slip invincible mutant a hundred
我將一個無敵突變體一百個
viewer points for that image all rights
查看者為該圖像指出所有權利
for sending that in well take it yeah if
如果發送，那就好好接受它
you'd like some viewer points send me a
你想要一些觀眾點給我發一個
picture of you watching category 5 TV on
你看5類電視的圖片
your device whatever your device is and
您的設備無論您的設備是什麼和
certainly try to slip yourself into the
當然試著讓自己陷入困境
picture if you possibly can I understand
圖片，如果你可能我能理解
if you're if you're taking the picture
如果你是在拍照的話
yourself that's a little more difficult
你自己有點困難
but yeah perfect and some of our viewers
但是，是的，我們的一些觀眾是完美的
are you knew this week is this the first
你知道這周是第一次嗎？
time you've ever watched category 5 are
你曾經看過第5類的時間
you in the time live yeah I got let us
你在活著的時候是的，我讓我們
know we love to hear from you that would
知道我們很樂意聽到你的意見
be awesome so if you're new in the chat
如果你是聊天新手，那就太棒了
room right now say hey guys I'm new yeah
房間現在說嘿傢伙我是新的耶
I tell us we're going to give you a
我告訴我們，我們會給你一個
shout out that'd be great d tapio 63
喊出那個 偉大的龍頭63
just says hi Hillary hi thanks for
只是說喜歡希拉里嗨謝謝
saying hi thanks for being here see lots
嗨謝謝你 在這裡看到很多
of ever lots of wonderful people joining
很多很棒的人加入
us in the chat room tonight mm-hmm yes
我們今晚在聊天室mm-hmm是的
it torto stryger steve 5 slip 3d and
它torto stryger 史蒂夫5滑3d和
it's really hard to go through all the
這真的很難去通過所有 的
names cuz i know i'm gonna end up
名字因為我知道我會結束
leaving someone out of course yeah
離開某人當然是的
annoyance black i'm cameron better say a
煩惱黑色我是卡梅隆說的更好
jamison because he gets very very upset
賈米森，因為他非常沮喪
he's true a true blue fan and those who
他是真正的藍色粉絲和那些
are who are checking out the chat room
是誰在檢查聊天室
who are thinking hey how come he never
誰在想他怎麼來他永遠不會
mentions me and your you know your name
提到我和你 ，你知道你的名字
starts with one of the you know the mid
從你知道的一個中間開始
alphabet letters we usually start from
我們通常從字母開始
either dead or a so yeah in him so Rini
無論是死了還是他都是如此，所以里尼
hey jamison that's like okay let's see
嘿賈米森， 好吧，讓我們看看
who's around the midmark we've got to
誰是我們必須的中間標記
give gwg and jonathan little MN little
給gwg和jonathan 小MN一點
nice to have you here nobody who's in
很高興有你在這裡沒有人在
the chat room who's actually joining us
實際加入我們的聊天室
for the first time tonight and I've seen
這是我今晚第一次見到
lots of people coming and going
很多人來來往往
throughout the week just stopping by the
整個星期都在停靠
chat room just to say hey they love the
聊天室只是說嘿他們喜歡的
show and we appreciate hearing from you
表演，我們感謝您的回音
as well of course it doesn't always work
當然，它並不總是 有效
that that they can join us live thank
他們可以和我們一起生活謝謝
you time zone they're not that so and
你是時區他們不是那樣的
that's why we offer all the different
這就是為什麼我們提供所有 不同的
ways to watch you do and we've also got
如何看待你，我們也有
we've got Twitter you'll see there's
我們有Twitter你會看到那裡
yeah my twitter is at Robbie Ferguson
是的，我的推特是在Robbie Ferguson
Hillary's got twitter as well I'm out on
希拉里的Twitter的了，以及我出來
the tweet machine Hillary rumble fair
推特機器希拉里隆隆 聲公平
yep that's me and of course our show
是的，這是我，當然是我們的節目
itself if you want to follow the show is
本身，如果你想跟隨節目是
at category 5 TV do it yeah follow us on
在第5類電視上做它是的跟著我們
twitter you can follow us on on google+
twitter你可以關注我們google +
yes cat five dot TV / G Plus which
是貓五點TV / G Plus哪個
technically is my own personal account
技術上是我自己的個人帳戶
but it it's all about the show so you
但這一切都與節目有關
can follow us there I've got facebook on
可以關注我們那裡 我有Facebook
our website if you want to scroll down
我們的網站如果你想向下滾動
the page you'll see us there we are
您將在那裡看到我們的頁面
everywhere essential everywhere
到處都是必不可少
everywhere yeah you can run you can hide
到處都是，你可以跑，你可以隱藏
but you can't escape us we're everywhere
但你無法逃避我們無處不在
speaking of everywhere we will send a
說到處都會發送一個
year supply of batteries anywhere in the
每年供應電池的地方
world and I'm talking you know sometimes
世界， 我有時會說你
you get these contests I know Sulu wants
你知道蘇魯想要的這些比賽
to be in the shot get out of here so
在鏡頭中離開這裡
good are you as batteries in the future
你是好的未來電池嗎？
okay so eco alkalines are eco-friendly
好吧生態鹼是生態友好的
batteries they're alkaline batteries as
電池是鹼性電池
you can tell by the name it's it's not
你可以用名字告訴它不是
just a clever name
只是一個聰明的名字
our eco alkalines and what's cool is
我們的生態鹼和什麼是酷
that these batteries they use recycled
他們使用這些電池回收
material they work hard to keep these
他們努力保持這些材料
batteries environmentally sit down
電池環保坐下
eco-friendly is really the term green as
環保真的是綠色這個詞
far as that goes but also they offset
儘管如此，但他們也抵消了
their carbon footprint so what carbon
他們的碳足跡是什麼碳
footprint they do have with the
他們確實擁有足跡
manufacturing process is actually offset
製造過程實際上是抵消了
by the plantation of trees and whatever
通過種植樹木等等
else is necessary to to make sure that
否則有必要確保這一點
that that's offset so we have a year
這是抵消所以我們有一年
supply of batteries that we're giving
那我們給電池供電
away at the end of the month and I'd
走在月底 ，我會
love for you to participate in that
愛你參與其中
contest just go to cat five dot TV /
比賽只是去貓五點電視/
free batteries and you'll be able to
免維護蓄電池，你就可以
become eligible to win those is really
有資格贏得那些是真的
really simple all you have to do is you
真的很簡單你所要做的就是你
can like them on facebook you can follow
可以在 Facebook 上喜歡他們， 你 可以關注
them on twitter you can retweet the
他們在Twitter上你可以轉推
there's particular tweet that we have a
我們有一個特別的推文
link to at this website and if you
鏈接到這個網站，如果你
retweet it if you do all three of those
轉發它，如果你做了所有這三個
things you have three times the chance
你有三次 機會的東西
to win and and if you you know if you're
獲勝， 如果你知道你是否
not on facebook you can do two things on
不是在Facebook上你可以做兩件事
twitter if you're only on facebook you
推特，如果你 只是在facebook上
can like them on facebook there's all
可以在Facebook上喜歡他們所有
these different ways that you can
你可以用這些不同的方式
participate in the contest but there's
參加比賽，但 有
no really you know there's no having to
不，你真的沒有必要
sign up for anything or anything like
註冊任何東西或 類似的 東西
that it's really really simple to
它真的很簡單
qualify so make sure even if you're not
即使您 不是，也要確保資格
on Twitter or Facebook easiest thing to
在Twitter或Facebook最簡單的事情
do would be to sign up for twitter
我會註冊twitter
account and follow the show get on to
帳戶並按照節目繼續
cat5 TV / free batteries for your year
cat5電視/免費電池為您的一年
supply of free eco alkalines batteries
供應免費的生態鹼電池
awesome that would be so cool everyone
太棒了，每個人都會這麼酷
needs batteries that's what I say it's
需要電池就是我所說的
terrific you need batteries everyone its
太棒了你每個人都需要電池
batteries I need batteries he needs
電池我需要他需要的電池
batteries yes oh my lanta the fun is
電池是哦我的lanta樂趣是
just beginning I tell ya it's just
剛開始我告訴你它只是
starting I know loads of your questions
開始我知道你的問題
so i'll let you i'll let you take that
所以我會告訴你，我會讓你接受
away alright question number one come at
好吧問題排在 第一位
us from gizmo at work hey gives me what
我們從工作中的小發明嘿給我什麼
work hi all is it possible to monitor
大家工作是可以監控
how many devices are currently using my
目前有多少設備使用我的
Wi-Fi connection it could be interesting
Wi-Fi連接可能很有趣
to make sure nobody is using it without
確保沒有人使用它
me knowing thank you and keep on with
我知道謝謝你，繼續
work and he's coming from Montreal so
工作，他來自蒙特利爾
thanks for email from Montreal cool yeah
感謝來自蒙特利爾的電子郵件很酷
and definitely you can monitor that that
你肯定可以 監控那個
Wi-Fi connection I think that the
Wi-Fi連接我認為，
easiest thing to do because everybody's
最簡單的事情 ，因為每個人都這樣做
using you're using like a Wi-Fi access
使用你像Wi-Fi訪問一樣使用
point or a Wi-Fi router quite often
經常點或Wi-Fi路由器
times your router will contain some
你的路由器將包含一些
mechanism of being able to monitor who's
能夠監控誰的機制
connected to your Wi-Fi I think the best
連接到你的Wi-Fi我覺得最好
thing to do is to actually use your
要做的事情就是實際使用你的
router is going to be the most reliable
路由器將是最可靠的
because that's the actual you know the
因為那是你所知道的實際情況
access point to use the term that's
接入點使用的術語是
where all those connections are being
所有這些聯繫都在哪裡
made so that device can easily reflect
這樣設備可以很容易地反映出來
an accurate output as to what how many
準確輸出多少
people and who are actually connected to
人和實際 聯繫的人
your router I have a firmware installed
你的路由器我安裝了固件
on my router called dd-wrt it's dd-wrt
在我的路由器上叫dd-wrt它是dd-wrt
and i'll put links and everything in the
我會把鏈接和一切都放在
show notes for episode number 207 for
顯示第207集的註釋
you let me let me see if I can log into
你讓我告訴我是否 可以登錄
my router for you here just so that I
我的路由器就在這裡， 所以我
can show you how it works on my device
可以告訴你它在我的設備上是如何工作的
mm-hmm he's having some difficulty
mm-mm他有一些困難
remembering his passwords you've got so
記住他已經得到的密碼
many things going on it's hard to keep
許多事情都很難保持下去
them all straight yes sometimes I think
他們都是直接的，有時我想
my keyboard can't keep up with me that's
我的鍵盤跟不上我的意思
slightly true I believe it I've seen you
我相信我見過你
all I've brought up dd-wrt panel here
我在這裡提到了dd-wrt面板
and on the panel I've clicked on status
在面板上，我點擊了狀態
and wireless and I've pre click those
和無線，我已經預先點擊了那些
just in case there's anything privately
以防萬一有私事
identifying on the on the router itself
識別路由器本身
and you'll see if I go down here that
你會看到我是不是去了這裡
there are two devices currently
目前有兩種設備
connected to my Wi-Fi and you can
連接到我的Wi-Fi，你可以
actually click on that device and it
實際上點擊該設備和它
will tell you what it is so that's made
會告訴你它是什麼，所以這是
manufactured by Apple so that's that's
由Apple製造，就是這樣
going to be that's going to be my ipod
將會成為我的iPod
there it is it's connected to my Wi-Fi
在那裡，它連接到我的Wi-Fi
right now right so that's how dd-wrt
現在正確，這就是dd-wrt
presents it and one of the other cool
介紹它和另一個酷
features of dd-wrt that I love with
我愛的dd-wrt的特點
regards to wireless and this is great
關於無線，這很棒
from a system administrator standpoint
從系統管理員的角度來看
is it's got wit as our wives or whatever
它是否像我們的妻子或其他什麼一樣有智慧
you want to call it wife is actually
你想把它稱為妻子其實是
pre-configured in the
在...中預先配置
firmware and what this does once it
固件以及它曾經做過的事情
loads up it's going to actually show you
加載它會 實際顯示給你
a bit of an overview of your networks
稍微概述 一下你的網絡
and what's flying around your I think my
什麼在我周圍飛來飛去？
browser is kinda messed up there we go
我們去的瀏覽器有點搞砸了
each one of those little dots is
這些小點中的每一個都是
actually a device or a Wi-Fi network
實際上是設備或Wi-Fi網絡
nearby me you can find out information
在我附近，你可以找到信息
by bringing up the mac address and find
通過調出mac地址並查找
out more about it there's all different
關於它的更多信息有所不同
kinds of tools built into dbl dd-wrt
dbl dd-wrt中內置的各種工具
that are very very cool but to answer
這非常非常酷，但要 回答
your questions your your question the
你的問題是你的問題
router is going to have a perfect output
路由器將有一個完美的輸出
of that mine I love dd-wrt for that it
那個我喜歡dd-wrt的那個
allows you to not only see the devices
不僅可以讓您查看設備
that are connected here but it also
在這裡 連接 但它也
shows you their their signal quality the
告訴你他們的信號質量
status and you can copy that MAC address
狀態，您可以復制該MAC地址
and put it into a filter if you like
如果你願意，把它放進過濾器
because dd-wrt includes free Mac
因為dd-wrt包含免費的Mac
filtering so for example on my network
例如在我的網絡上過濾
if you brought your own laptop you
如果你帶了自己的筆記本電腦
wouldn't be able to connect because I
因為我無法連接
restrict by Mac filtering specific
限制由Mac過濾特定
devices so my ipod touch has a
因此我的ipod touch 有一個設備
particular mac filter or a mac address
特定的mac過濾器或mac地址
that is allowed on my network so any
我的網絡允許這樣任何
other mac address is not allowed so
其他mac地址是不允許的
that's that's another handy neat thing
這是另一個方便的東西
because you're not only just seeing the
因為你不僅僅是看到了
device you seen the mac address as well
你見過mac地址的設備
yeah cool thanks for the question I hope
是的，非常感謝 我希望 的問題
that I hope that helps but even if
我希望這有 幫助，但即便如此
you're not on dd-wrt your firmware might
你沒有使用 dd-wrt你的固件
have something within your wireless
你的無線網絡中有東西
section so go go take a look login can't
部分所以去看看登錄不了
read yeah check it out now um side note
讀是啊現在檢查一下你的旁注
just got a little hello coming to us
剛跟我們打招呼
from a skeptic thinker first time
來自懷疑論者的第一次
watching the show live although watch it
雖然看著它，但看現場直播
before from India sorry thank you thanks
來自印度之前抱歉謝謝謝謝
for watching yeah it's so nice to have
看是的，這真是太好了
you here um it must be a hard time in
你在這裡，你一定很難過
the morning in India I would think
我想在印度的早晨
probably fantastic they are you staying
可能很棒他們你住的
up for us and nice to have you here and
為我們而且很高興有你在這裡
yeah great yeah from poon
來自poon，是的，非常棒
yeah what was the name again on that um
是的，那個名字又是什麼名字
skepta thinker skepta thinker yes so
skepta思想家skepta思想家是的
nice to have you here yeah yeah thanks
很高興有 你在這裡是的，謝謝
for coming okay back to business got me
為了 好好回到生意來找我
a question here from Catherine McCleary
凱瑟琳麥卡勒里的一個問題
before sorry before I don't normally
前對不起之前，我做不 正常
like to interrupt but just because
喜歡打斷但是因為
there's some chatter in the chat room to
聊天室裡有一些聊天
people saying oh but Mac filtering is
人們說哦，但Mac過濾是
easy to bypass and things just to touch
容易繞過和触摸的東西
on that yeah Mac filtering is a nice
在那，是的Mac過濾是一個很好的
supplement to wpa2 it's it's a nice way
補充wpa2這是一個很好的方式
to further enhance your security it's
為了進一步增強您的安全性
not the only security that you'll use
不是你將使用的唯一安全性
you'll have wpa2 you'll have your SSID
你有wpa2你將擁有你的SSID
hidden and you'll have mac filtering so
隱藏，你將有mac過濾所以
with those three things in place it's
有了這三件事就好了
quite probable that even if someone was
很可能的是，即使有人在
prying they wouldn't even know that
他們甚至不會知道這一點
you're your network was available they
你是他們的網絡
wouldn't even see your network because
甚至不會看到你的網絡因為
you've got all those three things in
你已經擁有了這三件事
place and you're able to block them at
地方，你可以 阻止他們
every level the SSID being hidden means
隱藏SSID的每個級別都意味著
they won't be able to see your your
他們將無法看到你的
network the mac filter being enabled and
網絡啟用的mac過濾器和
set the specific devices means they
設置具體設備意味著他們
won't be able to connect by default they
他們默認無法連接
won't be able to connect in order to
將無法連接以便
enter a password and then the wpa2
輸入密碼，然後輸入wpa2
encryption is going to protect so that
加密將保護這一點
if they do get past those original if
如果他們確實超過了那些原件
they are able to circumvent those then
他們能夠繞過那些
there's something in place that's fairly
有些東西是公平的
strong that's going to protect you even
強大的，甚至會保護你
further so it's about having multiple
進一步，這是 有多個
things in place I'm not saying just turn
事情到位我不是說轉身
on Mac filtering and leave it as is that
在Mac上過濾並保持原樣
would be dangerous for you thank you for
對你來說會很危險，謝謝你
bringing that up in the chat room sorry
把它帶到聊天室對不起
yes sure to step on the other but thanks
是的，肯定會踩到另一個，但謝謝
for addressing that for sure definitely
肯定地解決這個問題
good to know um okay so our next
很高興知道你好， 所以 我們的下一個
question Catherine McCleary rights to us
問Catherine McCleary對我們的權利
saying Commodore usa.net our
說Commodore usa.net我們的
manufacturing all-in-one linux based
製造一體化的基於Linux的
computers just add a monitor when to
計算機只需添加一個監視器
make the look of the classic Commodore
看看經典的Commodore
64 vic-20 and coming soon ameda
64 vic-20即將推出ameda
computers they also will eventually
計算機他們也將最終
allow one to play classic c64 in amiga
允許一個人在amiga中玩經典的c64
games via a Malaysian with one button
通過馬來西亞人用一個按鈕進行遊戲
access to c64 mode at least on the c64 X
至少在c64 X上訪問c64模式
they apparently make use of technology
他們顯然利用了技術
developed for laptops to fit all the
為筆記本電腦開發適合所有的
guts
膽量
of a computer into a form factor not
將計算機 變成外形而不是
much larger than the keyboard itself
比鍵盤本身大得多
these machines seem pricey for what is
這些機器看起來很昂貴
included hardware wise however as a
然而，包括硬件明智
former owner of several c-54s and a c128
曾經擁有幾架c-54和一架c128
and an Amiga 500 I'm still intrigued by
和 Amiga 500我仍然很感興趣
the concept my question is have any of
這個概念我的問題是什麼
the cat5 TV staff or viewers tried the
cat5電視台的工作人員或觀眾試過了
vic-20 or c64 X Linux box all-in-one
vic-20或c64 X Linux盒一體機
computers from Commodore USA net and if
來自Commodore USA net的電腦和if
so what do you think of them and I'd
那麼你怎麼看待他們呢？
love for fans of the classic see Sophie
喜歡經典的粉絲見索菲
for an immediate gains oh and would fans
為了立即獲得哦， 粉絲們
of these classic games be better served
這些經典遊戲可以更好地服務
by just running an emulator software on
只需運行模擬器軟件即可
their existing hardware instead of
他們現有的硬件而不是
buying those linux boxes which look like
買那些看起來像的linux盒子
old computers that you still up one of
舊計算機，你還是其中之一
the one of the things that I love about
這是 我喜歡 的事情之一
that mock commodore system is that like
模擬商品系統就是 這樣
the c64 the the keyboards were so much
c64的鍵盤非常多
different the action on those keyboards
這些鍵盤上的動作不同
it's like the old IBM licked the 80
這就像舊的IBM舔了80
keyboards they just were there was
他們剛剛在那裡的鍵盤
something about them the action on them
一些有關他們 對他們 的行動
was really really nice the Commodore 64
Commodore 64真是太棒了
keyboard if they've been able to
鍵盤，如果他們能夠
successfully mimic not just the look but
成功地模仿了外觀但是
also the the responsiveness of that
也是那種反應
keyboard I think that would be pretty
鍵盤我覺得這很漂亮
incredible from a nostalgia standpoint I
從懷舊的角度來看，這令人難以置信
think it looks like an incredible device
認為它看起來像一個令人難以置信的設備
in that it's it's one awesome case mod
因為它是一個很棒的案例mod
if you will but yeah I mean you're
如果你願意，是的，我的意思是你
looking at a thousand dollars for the
看著一千美元
base model really when it comes down to
基礎模型真的歸結 為
it and and $1,500 for one that has an i7
它和一個擁有i7的 1,500美元
in it so the specs can be very good but
在它，所以規格可以非常好，但
you're still looking at a small form
你還在看 一個小表格
factor system and you know I don't know
因素系統，你知道我不知道
what they're doing to cool it and
他們正在做些什麼來冷卻它
everything like that but I like the c64
一切都那樣，但我喜歡c64
addition the Commodore 64 though the you
另外Commodore 64雖然是你
know the traditional this one here right
在這裡知道傳統的這個
it looks very very classic Commodore but
看起來非常非常經典Commodore但是
I was disappointed to find that there
我很失望地發現那裡
Vic model they're creating the the slim
維克模特他們正在創造苗條
and it doesn't look at all like Leah no
它看起來並不像 Leah 那樣
it's not affect when t by any stretch
它在任何伸展時都不會受到影響
but it's pretty cool that an entire
但整個都很酷
computers fit into that keyboard but it
電腦適合那個鍵盤，但它
doesn't at all take me back
根本不會把我帶回來
nostalgically like the Commodore 60
懷舊地喜歡Commodore 60
for model that they're using its
對於他們正在使用它的模型
Commodore usa.net and you know i would
Commodore usa.net，你知道我願意
think that their target market is not
認為他們的目標市場不是
the average end user gamer i think it's
我認為平均最終用戶遊戲玩家
going to be more the nostalgic rich dude
將成為更多懷舊的富人
you know what i mean like it it's really
你知道我的 意思是它真的
if you're gonna slap fifteen hundred
如果你要打了 一千五百
dollars into a computer you're not going
美元到 你不去的電腦裡
to get one that's just oh look at that
得到一個 只是哦看看那個
that's that's a really cool yeah you
那是你真的很酷的耶
might as well pick up at a garage sale
不妨去車庫買賣
for two bucks an old vic 20 and rip out
兩塊錢，一個老維克20並撕掉
the insides and put an atom board in it
內部並放入原子板
and you know then you'd have something
然後你知道 你有什麼東西
that you can show off to your friends
你可以 炫耀給你的朋友
anyways but if you've got the money I
無論如何，但如果你有錢我
think they're appealing to a completely
認為他們完全吸引人
different different market I have not
不同的市場，我沒有
tried one to answer the viewers question
試過一個回答觀眾的問題
there um anyone in the chat room I don't
我沒有在聊天室裡的任何人
know how their sales are or whether it's
知道他們的銷售情況是否如此
whether it's been happening for them I
是否一直在為他們發生我
think it's a neat idea i think
我認為這是一個很好的主意
nostalgically it would be it would be
懷舊地，它會是
something that i would enjoy having on
我喜歡的東西
my desk but i could not see spending
我的辦公桌， 但 我看不到消費
that kind of money on justify that
那種錢證明了這一點
exactly yeah well these specs are pretty
確切地說，這些規格很漂亮
good yeah i mean like i say there's an
好的是的我的意思就像我說有一個
i7 available for 1,500 bucks and it's
i7可以獲得1,500美元的價格
pretty decent you know the specs are all
相當不錯，你知道規格都是
right but yeah for what you get you're
對，但是因為你得到了什麼
paying for the nostalgia through the
通過這種方式為懷舊付出代價
teeth fair enough yeah and to quote
牙齒公平，是的，並引用
Weird Al as a Jamenson did you think
你覺得奇怪的阿爾作為詹姆森
your Commodore 64 is really neato what
你的Commodore 64真的很棒
kind of chip you got in there a Dorito
你在那裡得到的那種芯片Dorito
it's all about the Pentiums weirdo yep
它是關於Pentiums weirdo的全部
alright moving onward and upward oh look
好吧向前和向上移動哦看
at this little chestnut of an email i
在這個電子郵件的小栗子我
have here coming to us from Morton
我來自莫頓
obadiah David Daniel located in walled
obadiah David Daniel位於圍牆
amor Lima Israel this e-mail range as
amor Lima Israel這個 電子郵件的 範圍如下
followed hey Robbie thank for adduce
跟隨嘿羅比感謝adduce
part are Assad and forage heaven Flynn
部分是阿薩德和牧草天堂弗林
jet kill Jackie are given tail a leg an
噴射殺死傑基給了尾巴一條腿
to meet until Koontz board egg dimmed
直到Koontz 董事會蛋變暗為止
yet if you're wondering if you are in
但如果你想知道你是否在
English Oh
英文哦
I thought she was playing it backwards I
我以為她是在倒退我
might have been good night ha this is
這可能是晚安哈哈
actually better pull this is a very fun
實際上更好拉這是一個非常 有趣
email and throughout it our words that I
電子郵件，並貫穿其中我的話語
can identify such as Facebook Google
可以識別Facebook等谷歌
YouTube um vimeo um what else but
YouTube嗯vimeo 嗯，還有什麼
unfortunately i feel like my israeli i
不幸的是， 我覺得我的以色列我
believe that's what this is I'm not
相信這 就是我不是
actually sure ok it's probably not as
實際上確定它可能 不是那樣
good as it used to be likes probably not
好像以前可能不喜歡
one of my my top languages so I feel
我覺得我的頂級語言之一
like I might not be able to translate
就像我可能無法翻譯
this do you know some no oh I don't hold
這個你知道嗎哦，我不抱
my leg ha ok let's see if that's
我的腿好吧，讓我們看看是不是
actually a great email and I think it's
實際上是一個很棒的電子郵件，我認為是
quite fun and thank you for sending it
非常有趣，謝謝你發送它
maybe we can like what's mom translate
也許我們可以喜歡媽媽的翻譯
it online ok I've got to hear from
它在線確定我必須聽到
Morton ok so what I'm gonna show you
莫頓好，所以我要告訴你
something really cool ooh I'm gonna
真的很酷哦，我會的
highlight that entire email okay i'm
突出顯示整個電子郵件好嗎我
gonna copy it to my clipboard okay i'm
要把它複製到我的剪貼板好吧我
gonna bring up my internet browser
要打開我的網絡瀏覽器
whatever it may be gonna head on over to
無論它可能會轉向什麼
google the google machine that gave it
谷歌給它的谷歌機器
because google does this very well cool
因為谷歌非常酷
up the very top i don't know if you've
在最頂層，我不知道你是否已經
ever noticed this but they added this
曾經註意到這一點，但他們補充說
translate button way back in the days of
翻譯按鈕回歸的日子
Alta Vista and you'll notice that from
Alta Vista，你會注意到來自
is set to detect so we don't even know
設置為檢測，所以我們甚至不知道
need to know what the source language is
需要知道源語言是什麼
hmm two is set to English me so you know
嗯， 兩個是英語我，所以你知道
a lot of a lot of languages can look the
很多語言都可以看到
same as far as their semantics go
就他們的語義而言也一樣
especially when you get into different
特別是 當你遇到不同的時候
alphabets I find it's it's tough to
字母表我發現這很難
differentiate because I don't know the
區別因為我不知道
alphabets that are not you know like an
你不知道的字母表
English alphabet I don't know what the
英文字母我不知道是什麼
technical term is but so then I run into
技術術語是如此然後我遇到了
trouble and there are some interesting
麻煩，有一些有趣的
characters in this email so I'm going to
這封電子郵件中的字符，所以我要去
paste that in and you'll notice that
粘貼在，你會發現，
instantly google has detected that this
即時谷歌已經檢測到這一點
is an in fact Norwegian not it's really
實際上是挪威人，不是真的
like I thought and it's translated to
就像我想的那樣，它被翻譯成了
English that is awesome hey Robbie thank
英語很棒嘿羅比謝謝
you for responding so quickly to the
你這麼快就回應了
last communication I had for you
我最後的溝通對你而言
yesterday
昨天
notice that the maybe the grammar is not
請注意，可能語法不是
you know verbatim to what yeah yeah what
你知道什麼是耶，你知道什麼
you would say verbally but you can get
你會口頭上說，但你可以得到
the gist of what the email is asking the
電子郵件要求的要點
reason I want the opportunity to be able
我希望有機會的原因
to ask you about what I want with a
用你問我想要什麼
webcam is that I wish that some of my
網絡攝像頭是我希望我的一些
questions would be included in future
問題將在未來包括在內
sending or broadcast I would expect
我希望發送或廣播
because maybe someone else is wondering
因為也許別人在想
the same thing I want to start new
同樣的事情，我想開始新的
social networks like Facebook Google+
像Facebook Google+這樣的社交網絡
and others but the possibilities
和其他人，但可能性
possibilities that I saver on facebook
我在facebook上保存的可能性
and google+ do i use wordpress as a blog
和谷歌+ 我使用wordpress作為博客
platform to the aux oh i don't know what
平台的 輔助哦， 我不知道 是什麼
that is we're referring to um okay buddy
那是我們指的是好夥伴
pressure sounds like peer pressure to
壓力聽起來像同伴的壓力
have found software that creates
找到了創造的軟件
templates for WordPress which I've paid
我支付的 WordPress模板
for etc so it's it it does a pretty fair
對 等所以這是它確實一個非常公平的
job of me understanding okay well he's
我的工作理解還好，他是
asking about getting on social platforms
詢問上社交平台
and using WordPress in particular it's
特別是使用WordPress
paid for a template and is curious about
支付模板並且很好奇
you know whether they can continue using
你知道他們是否可以繼續使用
that to connect to other other system
那要連接到其他系統
other services and there are plugins for
其他服務和插件
that and wordpress for sure moving on in
那和wordpress肯定會繼續前進
the email and and I'd encourage you in
電子郵件，我會鼓勵你
no matter what language that you send us
不管你發給我們什麼語言
an email and this is of course a very
一封電子郵件，這當然是非常的
long email and that makes it difficult
長電子郵件，這使它很難
for us to to answer any one question but
我們要回答任何一個問題但是
but you can see how Google Translate has
但你可以看到谷歌翻譯有多少
given us an opportunity to be able to
給了我們一個機會
follow through with this and if I scroll
如果我滾動 ，請完成此操作
down in the email I'm just gonna and I'm
在電子郵件中，我只是要和我在一起
sorry to have to skip over your
很抱歉不得不跳過你的
questions here to some degree and that's
這裡有一些問題，那就是問題
largely because of the size of the email
很大程度上是因為電子郵件的大小
i'll ask you to scale it back a little
我會請你把它縮小一點
bit but i will review this after the
但是我會在之後回顧一下
show so that i can give you better
顯示，這樣我可以給你更好的
attention but i feel like as far as on
注意，但我覺得就像
the air goes it's going to be tough to
空氣變得艱難
get all of these questions but so i'll
得到所有這些問題，但我會
just scroll to the bottom of your email
只需滾動到 電子郵件 的底部即可
here in which you say let's see he says
在這裡，你說讓我們看到他說
if I were blessed with a good economy I
如果我有幸擁有良好的經濟， 我
would have bought a macbook but I have
本來會買一台macbook，但我有
an old Mac laptop which is completely
完全是一台舊的Mac筆記本電腦
useless because it has the old Mac OS by
沒用，因為它有舊的Mac OS
the way what solution do you use when
你何時使用什麼解決方案的方式
you translate from norwegian to english
你從挪威語翻譯成英語
thank you in advance for your help so i
提前謝謝你的幫助，所以 我
feel like i answered one of your
感覺我回答了你的一個
questions there check right at the
問題就在那裡檢查
bottom by the way what what do you use
你最喜歡什麼用途
to translate there
在那裡翻譯
you have it now if I wanted to I could
如果我願意，你現在就擁有它
then get rid of this text and I could
然後擺脫這個文本，我可以
say good evening I'm going to change
說晚安，我要改變
this it's automatically detected english
這會自動檢測到英語
and i'm going to change this to
我要改變這個
norwegian okay thank you for your email
挪威 好的，謝謝你的電子郵件
talk for repose didn't i will reply by
說休息沒有我會回复
email yet will sweat because it was
電子郵件還會因為它而流汗
quite lengthy 40 days i hope that that
相當漫長的40 天我希望那樣
you can understand why that is sincerely
你可以理解為什麼這是真誠的
Bobby so now I've got something that i
Bobby所以現在我有了一些東西
can send back language that is
可以發回的語言
understood by this particular viewer and
這個特定的觀眾理解和
it's fantastic that's the usability of
它的可用性非常棒
that is wonderful so give it a try it's
這很棒，所以試一試吧
translate google com or your region
翻譯谷歌com或您所在的地區
specific site for me it's
特定的網站對我來說
translate.google.com thank you for
translate.google.com謝謝你
thanks for the question I again I'm
再次感謝我的問題
going to go through that it's it's quite
要經歷它的確如此
linking act and I'll take care of y'all
連接行為，我會照顧你們
I'll see what I can come up with as far
到目前為止，我會看到我能想到的東西
as helping you through whatever issues
幫助您解決任何問題
it is that you're experiencing for sure
這是你肯定經歷的
alright well that time Robbie it's that
好吧那個時候羅比就是這樣
time take it away it's news time
時間帶走它的新聞時間
from the category 5 TV newsrooms a dream
來自5類電視新聞室的夢想
ban on selling June to older teenagers
禁止向年齡較大的青少年出售六月
has been lifted after 17 years the
17年後被解除了
classic video game was put on an index
經典視頻遊戲被放在一個索引上
of control titles in 1994 as it was
1994年的控制權如何
deemed likely to harm youth like
被認為可能傷害青少年
pornography sales of the old-school
老派的色情銷售
shoot-'em-up games were restricted to
射擊遊戲僅限於
adult only stores the rules have been
成人只存儲規則已經
relaxed because officials believe that
放鬆，因為官員們相信
doom is now only of artistic and
厄運現在只是藝術和
scientific interest and will not appeal
科學興趣， 不會上訴
to youngsters I know this to be true
對於年輕人我知道這是真的
because i bought a first gen nintendo
因為我買了第一代任天堂
and think that my kids would love it and
並認為 我的孩子會喜歡它，
they didn't no dice it's just not cool
他們沒有骰子它只是不酷
anymore old school not cool I don't know
再也不老了， 我不知道
homeboy in health and wellness news a
健康與健康新聞家庭男孩a
review of previous research has found
對以往研究的回顧發現
that eating high levels of chocolate
吃高水平的巧克力
could reduce the risk of coronary heart
可以降低冠心病的風險
disease and stroke according to the
根據疾病和中風
study published on the bmj website data
研究發表在bmj網站上的數據
from more than 114,000 patients
超過114,000名患者
suggested risk was cut by an astounding
建議的風險被驚人的減少了
one-third the researchers warned however
然而，三分之一的研究人員警告說
the same excessive consumption of
同樣過度消費
chocolate will result in other illnesses
巧克力會導致其他疾病
there's no winning okay and what is
沒有贏的好，什麼是
being called a critical situation
被稱為危急情況
scientists in the US have warned NASA
美國科學家警告美國宇航局
that the amount of so-called space junk
那個所謂的太空垃圾量
orbiting Earth is at a tipping point a
軌道地球正處於臨界點a
report by the National Research Council
國家研究委員會的報告
says the debris could cause fatal leaks
說這些碎片可能導致致命的洩漏
in spaceships or destroy valuable
在太空飛船或破壞寶貴
satellites it calls for international
衛星它要求國際化
regulations to limit the junk and more
規定限制垃圾等
research into the possible use of
研究可能的用途
launching large magnetic nets or giant
發射大型磁網或巨型磁鐵
umbrellas the debris includes clouds of
雨傘的碎片包括雲
miniscule fragments old boosters and
微不足道的碎片老助推器和
satellites some computer models show the
衛星的一些計算機模型顯示了
amount of orbital rubbish has reached a
眼眶垃圾量達到了一定程度
tipping point with enough currently in
當前足夠的臨界點
orbit to continually collide and create
軌道不斷碰撞和創造
even more debris raising the risk of
甚至更多的碎片提高了風險
spacecraft failures the research council
航天器失敗研究理事會
said this statement on Thursday a notice
週四發表聲明說這個聲明
appeared on the kernel.org website on
出現在kernel.org網站上
Wednesday informing visitors that the
星期三通知遊客
servers the servers that are housing the
服務器容納的服務器
Linux kernel source code
Linux內核源代碼
had been hacked earlier this month the
本月早些時候被黑客攻擊了
breach was discovered on Wednesday the
週三發現了漏洞
immediate concern in many users minds
許多用戶心中直接關注
was that the Linux kernel itself was
是Linux內核本身
hacked but rest assured this is not the
黑客但卻放心，這不是
case kernel developer John Corbett has
案例內核開發人員John Corbett
an extensive x.x can't speak an
廣泛XX不能說的
extensive explanation of how we know the
我們如何了解這一點的廣泛解釋
linux girl is safe and sound in which he
linux女孩安然無恙
states kernel.org may seem like the
各州kernel.org可能看起來像
place where kernel development is done
內核開發完成的地方
but it's not it's really just a
但它不是 真的只是一個
distribution point so when we say that
分配點，所以當我們這樣說
we know the kernel source has not been
我們知道內核源代碼還沒有
compromised on Colonel org we really
我們真的在上校組織中妥協了
know it and tanks could soon get night
知道它，坦克很快就能過夜
time and invisibility thanks to a
時間和隱形感謝a
cloaking device that masks their
掩蓋他們的隱形裝置
infrared signature developed by BAE
BAE開發的紅外簽名
Systems the adaptive technology allows
自適應技術允許的系統
vehicles to mimic the temperature of
車輛模仿溫度
their surroundings as you can see in the
你可以在周圍看到周圍的環境
image here it also can make a tank look
在這裡，它也可以使坦克看起來
like other objects such as a cow or car
像其他物體，如牛或汽車
one seen through heat sensitive scopes a
通過熱敏範圍看到的一個
high-tech camouflage uses hexagonal
高科技迷彩服使用六角形
panels or pixels made of a material that
由材料製成的面板或像素
can change temperature very quickly
可以很快改變溫度
about a thousand pixel panels each of
每個約一千個像素面板
which is 14 centimeters across are
這是14厘米
needed to cover a small tank the panels
需要蓋住一個小坦克的面板
are driven by onboard thermal cameras
由車載熱像儀驅動
that constantly image the ambient
不斷地對環境進行成像
temperature of the tanks surroundings
坦克周圍的溫度
this is projected onto the panel's then
然後將其投射到面板上
to make it harder to spot the cameras
使 相機 更難 發現
also work when the tank is moving bae
當坦克移動時，也可以工作
estimates that the technology could be
估計該技術可能是
ready to put in production within the
準備投入生產
next two years you can get these full
接下來的兩年你可以得到這些
stories online at category 5 TV /
5類電視在線故事/
newsroom the category 5 TV news room is
新聞室5類電視新聞室是
researched by roy w Nash with
由roy w Nash研究
contributions fire fabulous community of
貢獻火災神話般的社區
viewers if you have a new story you
觀眾，如果你有一個新故事
thanks worthy of honorary mention send
感謝值得榮譽獎 送 的
us an email at newsroom at category 5 TD
我們在新聞室的第5類TD發送電子郵件
from the category 5 TV news room I'm
來自5類電視新聞室我是
Hillary rumble that is so cool very cool
希拉里隆隆聲很酷 很酷
very cool also now really yeah like
非常酷也現在真的很喜歡
that's wild that they can manipulate
那是他們可以操縱的狂野
heat because it makes sense that night
因為晚上才有意義
vision uses infrared heat
視覺使用紅外線加熱
so they can manipulate that heat into
所以他們可以操縱那些熱量
making it look like it's a car that's
讓它看起來像是一輛汽車
pretty wild just sitting there in the
非常狂野只是坐在那裡
field make it look like a cow well
田野讓它看起來像一頭牛
there's a cow just kidding which I think
我想是開玩笑的小牛
that would be more difficult I would
那會更 困難
think because they would have to make it
想想因為他們必須做到這一點
look like it yeah moving lame not that
看起來好像 是跛腳不是那樣
account moves like that but if it's if
帳戶會像那樣移動，但如果是的話
it's just standing kind of still they
它只是站在他們身邊
might get suspicious no that's pretty
可能會懷疑不是那麼漂亮
impressive technology that stuff like I
像我這樣令人印象深刻的技術
don't know you would see like
不知道你會看到什麼樣的
conceptualizing like films from years
從多年來的概念化電影
ago and they did it it's becoming it was
以前，他們做到了它正在成為它
called Star Trek Star Trek invented
名為Star Trek Star Trek的發明
everything which which is pretty awesome
一切都非常棒
I'd say how many things can you think of
我想說你能想到多少事情
that we're invented on Star Trek before
我們之前在“星際迷航”中發明過
before they ever came out it's like the
在它們出現之前它就像是
utter now reality the tablet pc that you
現在說你真實的平板電腦
know the the ipad that we're using the
知道我們正在使用 的 ipad
ipod touch it's like you see these
ipod touch就像你看到這些
things on old episodes of Star Trek
星際迷航舊劇集中的事情
before that kind of technology was even
在那種技術出現之前
fathom abble mm-hmm so in honor of our
為了紀念我們，我深深感謝mm-hmm
ode to Star Trek what are we gonna do
對星際迷航的頌歌我們要做什麼
we're gonna animate the whole thing
我們要為整個事情製作動畫
first of all this episode of category 5
首先是第5類的這一集
technology TV is brought to you in part
科技電視部分帶給你
by pogoplug at cat five dot TV /
通過pogoplug在貓五點電視/
pogoplug and of course planet calypso
pogoplug， 當然還有行星calypso
the free online game is available for
免費在線遊戲可用
you to download at cat five dot TV /
你下載貓五點電視/
Calypso this is category 5 technology TV
Calypso這是 5 類 技術電視
i'm your host Robbie Ferguson now I'm
我現在是你的主持人Robbie Ferguson
Hillary rumble and tonight we're gonna
希拉里隆隆聲，今晚我們要去
be looking at something that I've wanted
看著我想要的東西
to do for quite some time because I just
做了很長一段時間，因為我只是
thought it'd be fun I mean we talked
我覺得這很有趣我的意思是說話
about some video production features on
關於一些視頻製作功能
on linux and using free software to do
在linux上並使用免費軟件來做
those video productions we've looked at
我們看過的那些視頻作品
open shot video editor and and that's a
開放視頻編輯器， 這是一個
fantastic application which we're going
我們要去的奇妙應用
to get back into but then you showed up
重新開始，然後你出現了
with these star trek figurines would you
這些星際跋涉小雕像你會
you didn't ever realize that we'd
你沒有意識到我們會這麼做
actually find it useful I didn't know I
實際上發現它有用我不 知道 我
just saw that already don't like them
剛看到 已經不喜歡他們了
well she knows because I actually have
她知道，因為我確實有
like like within arm's reach I'm not I
就像在手臂範圍內一樣， 我不是我
don't you have to go off camera
你不必離開相機
and I have like you know I can i can
我想你知道 我能
grab communicator pins and tricorders
抓住溝通者的針腳和三輪車
and everything else so it's only fitting
和其他一切所以它只是合適的
tab I'm figures to accompany his it's
tab我是數字伴隨他的
only fans collection okay thanks for
只有球迷收集好感謝
that you're welcome i'm going to jump
你很歡迎我會跳
into synaptic package manager this
進入突觸包經理這個
software is available on any linux
軟件可在任何Linux上使用
computer linux is a free operating
電腦linux是免費的
system it's an alternative to mac OS or
系統它可以替代mac OS或
Windows and it gives you access to lots
Windows和它可以讓您訪問很多
and lots of free software within
和許多自由軟件
synaptic package manager what I'm going
突觸包經理我要去的地方
to do is just type in simply I it was
要做的就是簡單輸入它
called stop motion all one word I've
我所說的所有單詞都叫做停止運動
already installed it just to save myself
已安裝它只是為了保存自己
some time perfect thanks what you would
一段時間完美感謝你的意願
do is install that tool I'm here in is
這樣做是 為安裝工具，我在這裡
or an OS which is Anna blue to
或安娜藍色的操作系統
derivatives and you'll see stop motion
衍生品，你會看到停止運動
is there creating stop motion animations
是否有創建定格動畫
with images grabbed from your or
從你或你的圖像中抓取圖像
whatever okay with that software here's
不管這個軟件 還好嗎？
what's so cool and I thought about okay
什麼是如此酷，我想好了
well how are we gonna do this we're
那麼我們怎麼做呢？
gonna use our our best camera and go all
要用我們最好的相機然後全力以赴
out and make a state-of-the-art awesome
出來，做一個最先進的真棒
video because we could if we have the
視頻，因為我們可以，如果我們有
time truth is I know that most people
時間 真相是我知道大多數人
don't have that kind of gear most people
沒有 那種裝備大多數人
don't have the ability to probably do
沒有能力去做
this in in 1080p so what we're gonna do
這是在1080p所以我們要做的
is we're going to be realistic with this
是我們要與 這個 現實
tonight we're gonna say okay this is
今晚我們會說這是好的
what you can do with your kids this is
你可以用你的 孩子 做些什麼
what you can do just at home if you're
如果你在家 ，你可以做些什麼
if you're just thinking hey this would
如果你只是想，嘿，這會
be a fun project yeah doesn't have to be
是一個有趣的項目是的，不一定是
a star trek figurine I mean these are
一個星際迷航小雕像我的意思是這些
great but fully articulating people use
偉大但完全清晰的人們使用
Lego they use clay they use whatever
樂高他們使用粘土，他們使用任何東西
else to do these again get your eraser
否則再做這些得到你的橡皮擦
on your desk and make it skip around and
在你的桌子上，讓它跳過來
do a little dance whatever you want to
做任何你想要的舞蹈
do but to make this realistic for you
不過要為你做到這一點
tonight what I have oh and sorry for
今晚我有什麼哦對不起
that I've got the big screen up there
我那裡有大屏幕
but what i have i've got my action
但是，我有我的行動
figure which you purchased for two
你為兩個人購買的數字
dollars two dollars at the dollar store
在美元商店的美元兩美元
$16 but you know it's not it's not a
16美元，但你知道這不是一個
it's not a huge investment no fantastic
這不是一項巨大的投資，也不是太棒了
anyone could do it and I've got a
任何人都可以做到這一點，我有 一個
classic logitech quickcam just an old
經典的羅技quickcam只是一個舊的
USB webcam all right for our backdrop we
USB攝像頭可以用於我們的背景幕
don't want to have my shoulder in the
不想讓我的肩膀在
back
背部
see Knightley and I could do this but
看看奈特莉，我可以這樣做但是
what I'm going to do instead keep things
我要做什麼而不是保留東西
simple I've got the cardboard box from
簡單的我已經得到了從紙箱
my motherboard perfect perfect now we
我的主板完美完美吧
are producing professional video just
正在製作專業視頻
like they do in Hollywood well you've
就像他們在好萊塢做的那樣
got an action figure over there I've got
我得到了一個動作人物
sooo you've got you've got Scotty beam
所以你已經得到了Scotty光束
me up Scotty alright so I've got my
我好斯科蒂好吧所以我得到了我的
quick cam in place and I'm going to on
在地方快速凸輪和我要上
the screen while you're working on that
在你工作時屏幕
I'm going and this is the official
我要去，這是官方的
unboxing video of Scotty laddie the
Scotty laddie的拆箱視頻
official under Chinese leaving the box
中國官員正在離職
there we go no longer a collectible yeah
那裡我們不再是收藏品了
just whatever you do don't tear it it
無論你做什麼都不要撕掉它
could double its value okay I'm gonna go
可以加倍它的價值好吧我要去
into sound and video and stop motion
進入聲音和視頻並停止運動
here we go dad was crying right now it's
在這裡，我們去爸爸現在哭了
okay God well I don't get another one
好吧，上帝好，我沒有得到另一個
first time in stop-motion i'm going to
第一次停止動作我要去
go settings configure stop motion and
去設置配置停止運動和
you'll see that it's detected my quick
你會看到我的快速檢測到它
cam so that's fine and so i can apply
凸輪，這樣很好，所以我可以申請
and hit close it's going to use that
並且關閉它將使用它
camera I and I click on this little
相機我和我點擊這個小
camera icon that's there it looks like a
相機圖標，它看起來像一個
video camera when I click on that is
當我點擊它時的攝像機
going to activate my quick cam Oh
要激活我的快速攝像頭哦
perfect there we go so this is actually
我們走的完美，所以這實際上是
live let's see whoa how are you making
讓我們看看你是怎麼做的
out there oh you gobble twist ties but
在那裡哦，你吞噬扭曲的領帶但是
we're right we're getting here well I
我們是對的，我們 來得很好
can get started yes so a couple of quick
可以開始是的，所以幾個快
things you'll notice here it says mix so
你會注意到的事情就是混合所以
what's going to happen is that my frames
會發生什麼是我的框架
are going to get mixed on the screen so
會在屏幕上混淆所以
that I cannot just see one of the one of
我不能只看到其中一個
the problems with stop motion is well
停止運動的問題 很好
how do I know that it gets move just a
我怎麼知道它只是一個移動
little bit how do I know that it's in
我怎麼知道它在裡面
the right position yeah with mex you're
正確的位置是啊，你是mex
able to actually see that i'm going to
能夠真正看到 我要去
show you how that works I get my guy
告訴你如何運作我得到了我的傢伙
let's start off screen there we go take
讓我們從那裡開始屏幕
one picture by clicking on the camera or
單擊相機或一張圖片
hitting your spacebar I'll use the
打你的空格鍵我會使用
spacebar just for kicks chair I'm going
空格鍵只是踢腿椅我要去
to move him in just a little bit space
讓他進入一點點空間
movement a little bit more and you see
移動一點點 ，你會看到
how it's starting to ghost
它是如何開始鬼的
oh you're making a lot of noise over
哦，你發出很多噪音
there ok moving them in a little bit
有好動他們一點點
more and hit space and now i'm going to
更多， 並打空間，現在我要去
start articulating them so that it looks
開始闡明它們以使它看起來
a little bit more real so i move them
更真實，所以我移動它們
just a little bit you can see that what
只是一點點，你可以看到什麼
is actually happening here is a bit of
實際上這裡發生的是一點點
ghosting that's the mix that's happening
重影，這是正在發生的混合
so i'll hit space I've got it now I move
所以我會打的空間，我想起來了 我謹
them just a little bit more okay move
他們更多的只是一點點好招
his arm just a little bit and I can
他的胳膊只是一 點點，我可以
actually see both images so that I know
實際上看到這兩個圖像，所以我知道
that I haven't gone like that because
我沒有那樣，因為
that's just gonna look so I can kind of
那隻是看起來我可以這樣
line it up and even if he falls out of
排隊，即使他失敗了
the shot I can put him back to where I
拍攝我可以把他帶回我的地方
think ok well there's where he was
好好想想他在哪裡
there's where he should be in the next
還有的地方，他應該是在 未來
frame hit space to grab the next shot
框架命中空間抓住 下一個鏡頭
and then keep going ok how are you
然後繼續說好你好嗎？
making out yeah I'm going I'm going
做出來是的我要走了
along I just move yeah childproof
沿著我只是移動是的防止兒童
packaging ok I've moved his arm down a
包裝好吧我把他的胳膊放了下來
little bit and moved him over ok move
一點點，讓他感動好動
down his leg spectron they're driving ok
沿著他的腿部光譜，他們正在開車
and space and women just a little bit
和空間和女人只是一點點
more and a little bit of more
更多，更多一點
articulation we're not getting all that
清晰度我們沒有得到所有這些
fancy where that you can spend more time
想像你可以花更多的時間
of course but we're going to make it so
當然，但我們要讓它如此
that it you know it's he's going to move
它你知道它會移動
very unnaturally into the screen this
非常不自然地進入屏幕這個
time I'm going to turn his head just a
時間我只想轉過頭來
little wee bit for the next frame and
對於下一幀而言，我們有點小小的一點點
again
再次
moved his hands a little bit maybe a bit
他的手稍微移動了一下
too much that's all right there we go
我們去的地方太多了
are you gonna catch up soon I'm Scotty
你很快就會趕上我斯科蒂
stuck in the dressing room he's got to
他被困在更衣室裡
get ready for his on-camera experience
為他的相機體驗做好準備
dropped his gun oh man okay if they
放下他的槍哦男人好吧，如果他們
could see me now hey take a look at me
現在可以看到我嘿看看我
now all those kids that used to make
現在所有那些曾經做過的孩子
funny and say Robby Robby great the
好笑，說羅比羅比很棒
dolls Robbie plays with dolls yeah but I
娃娃羅比和玩偶一起玩，但我
make awesome stop motion video it's an
製作令人敬畏的停止動畫視頻吧
action figure yeah it's an action figure
行動人物是的，這是一個行動人物
get it right okay see what I'm doing is
做得對， 好吧，看看我在做什麼
I'm articulating him just a little bit
我只是向他表達了一點點
and then putting him into a position
然後 把他放到一個位置
that is just a little bit moved all
這只是一點點感動
right how's he coming help well if he's
如果他是的話，他會如何得到很好的幫助
if he's not it doesn't have to be
如果他沒有也必須
perfect hell I know I know I just don't
完全地獄我知道我知道我不知道
want his pants to fall down but oh
希望他的褲子掉下來哦哦
that's good idea re he's ready he's got
這是個好主意，他已經準備好了
a double gun thing all right so get him
雙槍的事情好吧所以得到 他
in there so she slowly you want to
在那裡，所以她慢慢地想要
animate him into the set and I'm you
讓他進入場景，我就是你
know I can't articulate this guy too
知道我也無法表達這個人
much as I'm cuz I'm not that good at it
就像我因為我不是那麼擅長
here we go okay okay you're ready to
在這裡，我們沒事， 你準備好了
kind of make your way into the set I'm
有點進入我的方式我的方式
gonna move just one little degree there
那裡會移動一點點
turn him just a little bit are you
轉過身來，他只是一點點
stepping in okay okay here she comes a
踩好沒關係，她來了
little bit got the cat little bit more a
有點兒讓貓多了一點
little bit more okay oh okay oh there we
更好一點哦，好吧哦，我們
go okay so stop I'm gonna take a shot
好吧，所以停下來我會開槍
okay now we're gonna move one I gotta
還好現在我們要招一個，我得
turn a little bit yeah turn his head
轉了一下，是的，轉過頭來
well maybe moved his arm so you can see
好吧也許移動他的手臂， 你可以看到
that i can i can realign his arm see how
我可以調整他的手臂，看看如何
I messed up his arm I can put it there I
我弄亂了他的手臂，我可以把它放在那裡
can because I can actually see where his
可因為我能真正看到他的位置
arm was in the previous shot so have you
手臂是在上一次拍攝，所以你
moved a little bit that's kind of blurry
移動了一點，這有點模糊
well the blur is actually seeing the
好吧，模糊實際上看到了
show yet two frames three frames as a
顯示兩幀三幀作為
matter of fact so he moved a tad now
事實上，他現在感動了一點
okay a little bit more oh he's a sneaky
好吧多一點哦，他是鬼鬼祟祟
one he's moving real slow well
一個他正在慢慢移動
ok well get into the shot ok Yin yeah
好吧進入拍攝好尹耶
okay notice that I'm not taking the time
好的，請注意我沒有花時間
to do leg actions and so that's okay you
做腿部動作，這樣就沒事了
can spend more time as I say with your
可以花更多的時間，就像我對你說的那樣
kids and here you in yep shot I'm just
孩子們， 你們在這裡 拍攝我只是
hitting the spacebar to make this happen
擊中空格鍵以實現此目的
and we're we're about to have a duo I
而我們將要有一個二人組合
think but we're on the same team not in
我想，但是我們不在同一個團隊中
this movie okay then yep we go there
這部電影沒問題，那麼我們去那兒
nice to my face alright making making
我的臉很好，很好
your way in good
你的方式很好
there we go okay are you an see yea my
在那裡，我們沒事，你是一個看到我的
belt fell off that's okay drop trou one
皮帶脫落了，這是可以的
frame he won't have a belt okay get rid
框架他不會有皮帶好可以擺脫
of see this is where things can happen
看到這是事情可能發生的地方
like that you can just put them back
就像那樣你可以把它們放回去
where he should be okay call it
他應該好好稱之為
continuity during her yep there we go
她們在我們去的時候的連續性
yeah this is not a directed seen by any
是的，這不是任何人所看到的指示
means come on Starfleet oh hi got your
意味著來到Starfleet哦，你好了
finger in there awesome oh dear I didn't
手指在那裡很棒哦親愛的我沒有
realize that oh dear finger gun you have
意識到哦，親愛的手指槍你 有
yeah I'm good okay next next frame this
是的，我很好，下一幀這個
is this is action adventure this is
這是動作冒險嗎？
really like the old track it's it's slow
真的很像老賽道，這很慢
paced and poor special effects oh yeah I
節奏和可憐的特效哦是的我
hope you guys watching us having as much
希望你們看到我們一樣多
fun as we're swimming but just enough
我們游泳時很有趣，但足夠
see that blur is is you're seeing all
看到模糊是你看到的一切
three frame it's helpful to knit it
三個框架它有助於編織它
helps you to see where yeah you need to
幫助你看到你需要的地方
be
是
okay then let's make them hug no I don't
好吧那就讓我們擁抱吧，不，我不擁抱
know about that then I then I will be in
知道那個然後我會在那裡
trouble I'm I'm taking you down cuz
麻煩我是我把你帶走了
Sulu's very angry at Scotty today and I
蘇魯今天和我一起對Scotty非常生氣
forget who asked if it was a gamoto or
忘記是誰是gamoto或者
whatever but this Scotty has all his
除了這個斯科蒂有他的全部
fingers oh yeah yeah he was wondering if
手指哦是的是的他想知道是否
he do
他做
I'm gonna punch you if I hit you first
如果我先打你，我會打你的
never getting ridiculous okay so we need
從來沒有變得荒謬， 所以我們需要
to one of us needs to kind of articulate
我們中的一個人需要表達清楚
let's get down a little bit oh here I
讓我們下來 一 點點哦，我在這裡
get it oh no oh no let's looks like I'm
得到它哦哦不，不，讓我看起來像我
going down okay articulate the ending of
下去好的表達結束
our movie is trashed their way is the
我們的電影被摧毀了他們的方式
very okay so that leads me to oh dear
非常好，所以這導致我哦親愛的
okay what happens if that happens i can
好吧如果發生這種情況我會發生什麼
highlight frame number 43 there c43 with
突出顯示第43幀的幀號c43
the hand in the shot and then over here
拍攝的手然後在這裡
and I go remove that frame good okay now
我現在去除那個框架好了
that one's gone so now 42 a little bit
那個人現在已經42 了一點點
of hand in that I think you're good
因為我覺得你很好
that's just a shot of the 43 as it was
這只是43的照片
so put put your figure up you're good
所以把你的身材搞定你很好
there we go and one more frame what
在那裡，我們再去一個框架
about like a kicks we like oh sure kick
關於踢球，我們喜歡踢球
victory kick Oh what's happening I
勝利踢哦我發生了什麼事
messed this up big time no that was that
搞砸了這個很大的時間沒有那個
was probably me okay that's kind of like
可能我 還好，有點像
a victory is mine kind of thing I don't
勝利是我的一種我不喜歡的事情
know probably lay my arm down cuz I'm
我知道可能會放下我的胳膊
there we go okay there we go a little
在那裡，我們可以去那裡，我們去一點點
bit more
多一點
there we go okay good yep and I don't
在那裡，我們好好的，我沒有
know what now and I guess that's that's
知道現在是什麼，我猜那是那個
the end of the fellow k that's that's it
那個傢伙k的結束就是這樣
yeah I guess okay so what I'm gonna do
是的我想是的， 所以我要做的
I'm gonna switch out of camera mode i'm
我要退出相機模式了
gonna click on that big camera there
要在那裡點擊那台大相機
again toggle camera on off okay now down
再次切換相機開關現在好了
here you'll see your playback controls
在這裡你會看到你的播放控件
mm-hmm let's check out how we did are
mm-hmm讓我們來看看我們是怎麼做的
you ready I'm ready for this that's
你準備好了，我為此做好準備這
pretty good for our three second mini
我們的三秒迷你很不錯
movie but here's where it gets exciting
電影，但這裡是令人興奮的地方
we're gonna actually put that on
我們真的會把它放在上面
category 5 TV it's going to be output
5類電視它將被輸出
and rendered perfect on the show notes
並在演出筆記上呈現完美
for episode number 207 you're gonna
對於第207集，你要去
download it and just with your
下載 它，只需與你的
microphone with whatever device you want
麥克風與你想要的任何設備
to use record the voice over what is
使用記錄的聲音是什麼
actually happy that if you get a couple
真的很高興，如果你得到一對
of voices in there we might throw you
那裡的聲音我們可能會拋棄你
some bonus fewer points here's your
這裡的獎勵少了幾分就是你的
chance to be in on the Star Trek action
有機會參加“星際迷航”行動
we're going to give away a whole ton of
我們要放棄 一整噸
your points and you know how we work
你的觀點，你知道我們的工作方式
things around here we usually give stuff
這裡的東西我們經常給東西
away so check out the show notes for
因此請查看演出說明
episode number 207 a category five dot
第207集類別五個點
TV once it's up and you'll be able to
電視一旦啟動，你就可以了
participate in that contest you're going
參加你要參加的比賽
to find more information there well
在那裡找到更多的信息
that's that's fun though I could see
雖然我能看到，但這很有趣
that you know while we have no purpose
你知道的，雖然我們 沒有目的
or destination as far as that goes you
或者目的地就在你身邊
can have a lot of fun with that and I
可以和我一起玩得很開心
say it's but I could see myself actually
說它是，但我實際上可以看到自己
doing that with with the kids no baby be
和孩子一起做這件事沒有孩子
a lot of fun there so it's limitless as
這裡很有趣，所以它是無限的
to what you can do any could also if you
你能做什麼也可以
wanted to use like stickman drawings and
想要使用像火柴人的圖紙和
yeah oh yeah that's not really so the
是的哦，是的，那不是真的如此
next step what we want to do is simply
下一步我們想做的就是簡單
make sure that our project is save we're
確保我們的項目是我們保存的
going to go file save as and I'm going
要去文件保存，我要去
to slap it on my desktop as Trek fight
在Trek戰鬥時將它拍在桌面上
all right now we want to render it and
現在我們想要渲染它
we're going to go file export video
我們要去文件導出視頻
and now we're going to actually save a
現在我們要實際保存一個
video so what I'm going to do is I'm
視頻所以我要做的就是我
going to go Trek fight and you have to
要去Trek戰鬥，你必須
give it an extension it can be mp4 avi
給它一個擴展它可以是mp4 avi
whatever you want to do so i'm going to
無論你想做什麼，我都會這樣做
go dot avi and what that's going to do
去點avi和那將要做什麼
is this can tell it this is gonna be an
這可以告訴它這將是一個
audio video interleave there we go it's
音頻視頻交錯那裡我們去吧
been successful oh okay so bring up my
成功哦 好吧所以提起我的
desktop and you'll see that i have a new
桌面，你會看到我有一個新的
file they're called trek fight avi it's
文件他們被稱為艱苦跋涉戰鬥avi它
a video file being played in totem it's
一個正在圖騰中播放的視頻文件
good to go so that was what you're
很高興， 所以這就是你的意思
actually going to be able to download
實際上可以下載
off for our website and add your voice
關閉我們的網站並添加你的聲音
to okay we're going to be using free
好吧，我們將 免費使用
open-source software in order to
開源軟件才能實現
actually add your audio clips to that
實際上你的音頻剪輯添加到那
video so make sure you're watching as we
視頻所以請確保你正在觀看我們
receive enough entries for that we'll
我們會收到足夠的參賽作品
we'll be able to proceed with that
我們將能夠繼續這樣做
contest as well cool cool this is
比賽以及酷酷這是
category 5 technology TV you'll find us
您會找到我們的 5類技術電視
online triple w category five dot TV
在線三聯類五點電視
nice to have you here tonight and i'm
很高興今晚能有 你 ，我
your host of the show here cat Robbie
你的節目主持人羅比
ferguson nine Hillary Rumble I show up
弗格森9 希拉里 隆隆聲 我露面
randomly yeah I almost called myself
隨機是啊我差點叫自己
category five feet well he is category
類別五英尺井他是類別
five really let's be honest there you go
五，真的讓你說實話
yes so okay question um when people are
是的，所以好的問題，當人們
downloading this what sort of software
下載這個什麼樣的軟件
what they used to do voice up anything
他們曾經做過什麼聲音
you like you can use anything at all if
你喜歡你可以使用任何東西
you need to use a device you can use
你需要使用你可以使用的設備
like your your portable phone yeah yeah
就像你的便攜式電話一樣是的
yeah um you're gonna have no matter what
是的，你無論如何都會有
your platform is you're gonna have an
你的平台就是你要擁有的
audio recorder app so that's fine send
錄音機應用程序，所以很好發送
us a wave file send us a mp3 whatever it
我們一個wave文件發送給我們一個MP3無論如何
is OGG would be well maybe stick you a
是OGG也許會堅持你
couple viewer points if it's open source
如果它是開源的話，幾個觀眾點
whatever you do that's open source will
無論你做什麼，開源都會
give you a couple extra viewer points
給你幾個額外的觀眾點
absolutely it'll be a compounding so let
絕對是一個複合，所以讓
us know you know you will have the
我們知道你知道你會有
details in the show notes for 207 but
207的展示說明中的詳細信息
you'll let us know how you created the
你會告訴我們你是如何創造的
files and we will actually add it to the
文件，我們將實際添加到
video for you so you don't need to
視頻給你， 所以你不需要
compile it or anything like that hey if
編譯它或類似的任何東西，如果
we have like a bunch we can have our own
我們有一堆我們可以擁有自己的
little film festival sure I can play
我確實可以玩小電影節
them all yeah we could do that gang if
他們都是的，如果我們可以做那幫
you have a youtube account you could put
你有一個youtube帳戶，你可以放
it up yeah I want to master it yourself
它是的我想自己掌握它
that's cool too yeah
這太酷了，是的
something we'll see what happens with
這一點我們將看到會發生什麼
the viewers it's all up to you now it's
觀眾一切都取決於你現在的情況
all you it's all your creativity just
所有這些都是你的創造力
let the juices flow the sky's the limit
讓果汁流向天空是極限
here yep yes siree well hey I think we
在這裡，是的，是的，我很嘿，我想我們
pardon me recover quite a bit tonight oh
原諒我今晚恢復了很多哦
we did he always you know the time
我們做到了他總是讓你知道時間
always goes by so quick yeah sure does
總是如此快速，是的肯定
we've got a for those of you who are
我們為你們這些人提供了一個
watching the RSS feeds or we're we've
觀看RSS提要或我們是
got about five minutes just a little
只有一點點約五分鐘
more than five minutes left to the show
距離演出還有五分多鐘
so do we have any more viewer questions
那麼我們還有更多的觀眾問題
that we can actually we do again mom
我們其實 可以 ，我們再做媽媽
you're just gonna pull some up right
你只是要向右拉一些
here it's loading I know the
在這裡，我知道了
anticipations killing me um yep still
期待殺死我，是的
loading now if you want to send us an
如果你想 發送給我們， 現在 加載
email and a question how would you do
電子郵件和問題你會 怎麼做
that Robbie you just pop as an email
羅比，你只是彈出一個電子郵件
live at category five dot TV pretty easy
住在五類點電視很容易
stuff yeah that goes straight to hell
什麼東西，直接到地獄
and i will read it okay this isn't a
我會讀它好吧這不是一個
question actually but kind of a cool
問題實際上但有點酷
thing from invincible mutant i'm not
來自無敵突變體的東西我不是
sure how many of you would be interested
確定 你們中有多少人會 感興趣
in this kind of odd stuff i like gmail
在這種奇怪的東西我喜歡gmail
to be my default mail client therefore i
因此我是我的默認郵件客戶端
would like it to integrate well with my
希望它 與我的整合得很好
desktop i have the following scripts in
桌面我有以下腳本
my path that i can click on any mail to
我可以點擊任何郵件的路徑
link to launch my gmail and firefox but
鏈接啟動我的Gmail和Firefox但是
the problem is i don't have a clue on
問題是我沒有線索
how to make it integrate with the send
如何使其與發送集成
to function and nautilus in other words
換句話說，功能和鸚鵡螺
having a script that attaches file
有一個附加文件的腳本
straight from Nautilus to gmail i see
直接從鸚鵡螺到我看到的 gmail
and he sends a link there and some info
他發送了一個鏈接和一些信息
oh well I i could post the the script
哦，我可以發布腳本
that he's provided there come in the
那是他提供的
show notes for 207 sure and query if so
顯示207的註釋肯定和查詢，如果是這樣
you want to be able to like send to so
你希望能夠發送到那麼
you're not sending us then to function
你沒有發送我們去運作
like a file ah ok
喜歡文件啊好吧
I haven't ever done that so you're
我從來沒有這樣做，所以你是
you're looking to send a file attachment
你想發送文件附件
basically yes I'm gonna have to do a
基本上是的，我將要做一個
little looking up on that seems doable
看起來很少看起來可行
yeah oh yeah there's lots of stuff like
是的哦，是的，有很多像這樣的東西
it when I do a quick google search and
它當我做一個快速的谷歌搜索和
if anyone in the chat room has an answer
如果聊天室裡有人有答案
they can think certainly put it there
他們可以認為當然把它放在那裡
for you invincible mutant I don't off
為你無敵突變我不要
the top of my head know how that can be
我的 頭腦知道這 是 怎麼回事
done but I did a quick search for
完了，但我做了快速搜索
Nautilus send to email and first one
Nautilus發送電子郵件和第一個
that comes up is has got some
出現的是有一些
information about using a command called
有關使用命令的信息
Nautilus dash send to I don't know we
鸚鵡螺短跑發送給我不知道我們
have to look into it it I haven't done
它必須調查 它我沒有 做過
it before so nori about that well report
關於那份 報告 ，在此之前就是nori
back but yeah if if people in the chat
回來但是如果有人在 聊天
room have an answer for that I'd welcome
房間有一個答案，我歡迎
you to do that or I will do a little
你這樣做，或者我會做一點
research and find out for you okay we
研究並找到你好嗎我們
can do that cheers man we can do that no
可以做那個歡呼的人，我們可以做到 那個沒有
problem mm-hmm I'm just thinking so I
問題mm-hmm我只是在想我
can pull up another email in time this
可以及時撥打另一封電子郵件
comes to us from sunil question is I saw
從我看到的 sunil問題來找我們
your video on open shot video editor
你的視頻在開放式視頻編輯器上
great work I had a problem with using
偉大的工作我有使用的問題
blender though I copied all of your
攪拌機雖然我複制了你所有的
steps to unpack the blender and copy and
解壓縮攪拌機和復制的步驟
paste and Flander into the box blender
粘貼和Flander放入盒子攪拌器
executable executable and I get blender
可執行的可執行文件，我得到了攪拌機
error pop up box comes up when i try to
當我嘗試時出現錯誤彈出框
create and animate a title and he's
創建和動畫標題，他是
attached the screenshot which is very
附上截圖非常
helpful you can see that right here so
很有幫助，你可以在這裡看到
you've gone through the steps but it's
你已經完成了這些步驟，但確實如此
not working still some problems at 2.59
在2.59仍未解決一些問題
so that is current the the only thing I
所以這是我目前唯一的事情
could suggest is this this executive all
可以建議，這是這名高管全部
so that you've copied and pasted in the
這樣你就可以復制並粘貼了
executive all itself right not just yeah
行政人員本身就是正確的不僅僅是
that looks right and whatever the the
看起來右無論在
tail end of that is it's cut off
它的尾端是它被切斷了
just make sure like brows using Nautilus
只是確保使用Nautilus的眉毛
to this folder and just right click on
到這個文件夾，然後右鍵單擊
that blender file and and just make
那個攪拌機文件而且只是製作
absolutely certain that it's indeed
絕對肯定它確實如此
marked as executive all so that would be
標記為執行所有所以這將是
like under preferences you'll see that
喜歡在喜好下你會看到
let's see under permissions so you go
讓我們在權限下看到你去吧
into preferences and permissions and
進入首選項和權限
then there's one that says allow
然後有一個說允許
executing file as program just because
執行文件只是因為
it didn't sound to me like there were
它聽起來並不像我那樣
details about the actual error message
有關實際錯誤消息的詳細信息
or anything like that if I knew a little
或者類似的東西，如果我知道一點點
bit more about what it is like what kind
更多關於它是 什麼樣的
of behavior you're getting I'm expecting
你正在期待的行為
that's just not doing anything in which
那隻是沒有做任何事情
case that would be the first thing I
這將是我的第一件事
would check is making sure that its
會檢查是否確保它
executive otherwise it's not going to
執行，否則它不會
run right but if you have a specific
向右跑， 但如果 你有特定的
error let me know but another thing that
錯誤讓我知道，但另一件事
you can do is anytime you run a program
你 可以做的就是 你 運行程序的 任何時候
that you're getting an error and you're
你 得到了一個錯誤而且你是
not too sure what's going on in Linux
不太清楚Linux中發生了什麼
going to terminal and run that program
去終端並運行該程序
so for you it might be terminal and then
所以對你來說它可能是終點然後
type open shot so what happens then is
鍵入開打了那麼會發生什麼，然後是
that it loads open shot from terminal
它從終端加載開放射擊
but there it is it loads it in the GUI
但它是在GUI中加載它
but any errors that happen are going to
但任何發生的錯誤都會發生
be output to the screen in this window
在此窗口中輸出到屏幕
here so you'll be able to see what the
在這裡，你將能夠看到什麼
error is that's actually taking place
錯誤是實際發生的
and that will give you more information
這將為 您提供更多信息
unless it's giving you information on
除非它給你提供信息
the screen but that's another way that
屏幕，但這是另一種方式
you can find out with a linux
你可以找到一個Linux
application a little bit more about
應用更多 一點
what's taking place in the background so
這背景發生在什麼地方
good luck with that I hope that you're
祝你好運，我希望 你是
able to find it but post us more details
能夠找到它但發布更多細節
about the problem that you're
關於你的問題
experiencing and I'd be happy to to help
體驗，我很樂意提供幫助
you at that point Wow cool we're we're
你在這一點 哇涼的 我們我們
pretty near out of time that's it
非常接近時間就是這樣
yeah invincible mutant just saying you
是的無敵突變只是在說你
can chmod plus X the file that's the
可以chmod加上X的文件
terminal way of doing it and it
這樣做的終端方式和它
accomplishes the same thing as far as
完成同樣的事情
how that goes so yeah you can do that in
如何繼續下去所以是的，你可以做到這一點的
terminal as well if you like but with
如果你喜歡，也可以使用終端
GUI it accomplishes the same thing to
GUI它完成同樣的事情
mark it as executive all but yeah that's
把它標記為執行，但是是的
all the time that we have it's been
我們一直都是這樣的
great having you here thanks so fond of
非常感謝你，感謝你們
being here I had super super fun with
在這裡， 我有超級好玩的
this bad boy continue to get your
這個壞男孩繼續得到你的
questions into us live at category 5 TV
我們的問題生活在5類電視上
follow us on Twitter our twitter ID for
在Twitter上關注我們的推特 ID
the show is down there and of course you
這個節目就在那裡 ，當然還有你
can find any one of our hosts that are
可以找到我們任何一個主機
on Twitter through that through that
在Twitter 上通過那個
account and see that they are followed
帳戶並看到他們被遵循
there and yeah have a great week and
在那裡，是的，有一個美好的一周
we'll talk to you next Tuesday night
我們下週二晚上會和你談談
looking forward to bye-bye so yeah
期待 再見 所以，是的